Guide to the Records of Director of Academic Program Review, Barnett Hamberger 1972-2003 RG 9.7 RG 9.7
New York University Archives
- Series I
  - Scholars in Residence-General Information, 2002-2003 (Box 99, Folder 12)
  - Scholars in Residence-Pre-Semester Quesionnaire, 2002-2003 (Box 99, Folder 13)
  - Campus Diversity Study, 2001-2002 (Box 99, Folder 14)